winnipeghomefinder.com 2016-11-06

# Privacy Policy

We are committed to providing quality information within a trusted environment. Privacy and safety issues are important to us, and to that end we're pleased to offer a variety of links to Internet resources, within this website.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to me/us.

Personal information will not be disclosed to third parties without consent from the user.  I/we respect the security and privacy of our users.

### The Internet, Privacy, and Us

The Internet contains a wealth of information, unfortunately, it may also contain personal details about you that you don't want everyone to know. For example, your real name (lots of people on the Internet use aliases, alter egos or nicknames), street address, phone number, or e-mail address. When you go online, sites you visit may be gathering information about you without your knowledge. We strive to help our customers protect their privacy while using our services.

### Our Privacy Policy

Our policy is to respect and protect the privacy of our users. This policy statement tells you how we collect information from you and how we use it. Using the Internet should be a fun experience and we want to help you make it so.

The information you provide for your personal account is shared among the site as it is our goal to make your visits to our site easy and enjoyable. However, be assured that we will not disclose your personal information to any third parties without your consent. We may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other clients, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

We may share aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. For example, we will say our audience is x percent females and y percent males. This data is used to customize our content and advertising to deliver a better experience for our users.

There are cases where we may ask you for personal information such as your name, email and address. For example, we request personal information when you register as a member for the website.  We need to collect this information for fulfilling your request and tracking/verifying compliance with our policies as well as federal, provincial and local laws and/or for editorial and feedback solicitation purposes.

In case you change your mind or some personal information may change (such as your contact information), we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you give us.

### Opting-Out

Information provided at the time of submission from a user who is 18 years of age or over may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by us and our affiliates or companies that have been prescreened by us. To keep you in control of your personal information and the communications directed to you, we allow you to opt-out of the following services: sharing your information in our member directory, receiving communications from us about new features or services, and receiving communications about offers from third-party companies that offer a product or service that we think would be of value to you. If a user objects to such use for any reason, he/she may stop that use by e-mail request.

### Use of IP Address

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers -- the big computers that "serve up" Web pages -- automatically identify your computer by its IP address.

We may collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. When users request pages from our sites, our servers may log the guests' IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our house rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site, customers or others.

### Use of Cookies

What are cookies? Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them at most major Web sites.

By showing how and when guests use a site, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our users needs.

We have two primary uses for its cookies. First, we use them to specify unique preferences. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns. This helps us better understand and improve areas of the service that our users find valuable. While both of these activities depend on the use of a "cookie," visitors to our site always to have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. We do not use cookies to gather personal information like a person's name or e-mail address.  Any information gathered by the use of cookies is compiled on an aggregate, anonymous basis.

### Security

We place a high priority on security. Our computer system uses a combination of hardware and software designed to protect against unauthorized entry and loss, theft, or misuse of personal information. Although we will make every effort to protect personal information, no computer system is immune from hackers and others who might misuse information. We are not responsible for any breach of security that is beyond our reasonable control.

### Registration Forms

Personal information gathered from registration forms (such as name, email or street address) is used to send information related to our products and services to consenting parties. When you indicate that you want to receive a product or service, or contact a person or organization, we share the data needed for you to receive what you have indicated.

### Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains hyperlinks or "links" to other sites, and other sites may "link" to this site. Web sites linking to and from this site may have different privacy practices and policies from the ones described here. Visitors to our site should read the terms of use and privacy statements of other Web sites they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Users should be aware that when you are on our site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from our pages that take you outside our service. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information.

Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. We cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk.

Our policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond our control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.

### How to Get in Touch with us about this Privacy Policy

It's important to us to hear what visitors have to say about our services, and our policies. If site visitors have any questions, concerns, or complaints about this Privacy Policy, or want to let us know what they think about any of our off-line and on-line products and services, they can email us or call us.  Contact information is available on the Contact Page of this web site.

### Changes to this Internet Privacy Policy

I/We may, from time to time, make changes to this policy. We recommend that visitors to this site re-visit this privacy policy on occasion to learn of new privacy practices and changes to our policy.

### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
